http://www.marymaxim.com/privacy-policy/

Menu
YarnKnit & CrochetAfghansKnit AfghansCrochet AfghansSweatersKnit SweatersCrochet SweatersChildren's SweatersFashion AccessoriesSlippersShawls & WrapsPonchosHats, Scarves & MittensDoll Kits & DollsNeedles & HooksKnitting NeedlesCrochet HooksAccessories & StorageBabyAfghansApparelQuiltsPlastic CanvasPlastic Canvas KitsAccessories & SuppliesCraftsAccessories & ToolsAunt Martha'sBeaded BannersBeaded Kits & OrnamentsCalendarsDiamond DotzDiamond ArtFelt CraftsMacrameGeneral Craft KitsJewelry MakingKids Crafts & MoreLatch HookLatch Hook Rug KitsRug Yarn & AccessoriesNeedleworkQuiltingQuilt KitsNotionsQuilt SquaresHome DecorTable LinensPillowcasesAccessoriesPaint By NumberQuilt MagicYarn CraftsPuzzlesPatterns & BooksBooksApparelBaby & KidsDollsHome DecorHow To BooksQuiltingColoring BooksPatternsAfghan PatternsBaby PatternsCraft PatternsFashion AccessoriesLatch Hook PatternsPlastic Canvas PatternsSweater PatternsVintage PatternsYarn Craft PatternsHoliday PatternsFree PatternsPattern CorrectionsApparelGifts & ClubsClubs & Gift CardsFashion AccessoriesHome SolutionsReady Made ItemsSeasonalChristmasThanksgivingHalloweenEasterSpringSummerFallWinterClearanceNew Items
Account
Due to higher order volume and UPS, USPS and DHL all experiencing delays, there may be a 2-3 business day delay in processing and shipping of your order.
We apologize for the delay and thank you for your patience.
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from MaryMaxim.com (the “Site”).PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECTWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies:- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.- “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.Additionally, when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.Text Marketing and Notifications: By subscribing to MARY MAXIM mobile messages, you agree to receive autodialed marketing messages to the telephone number used at the time of opt in. Message frequency may vary. Message and data rates may apply. Consent is not required as a condition of purchasing any goods or services. In the event that you change or deactivate your mobile number, it is your responsibility to notify Mary Maxim at 800-962-9504 to have your number removed. Terms & Conditions are subject to change. The mobile carriers are not liable for delayed or undelivered messages. Text advertising keyword to 21387 to receive promotional alerts from Mary Maxim. Text STOP to 21387 to opt out.Text HELP to 21387, or call: 800-962-9504 for assistance.HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:Communicate with you;Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; andWhen in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Magento to power our online store--We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.You can opt out of targeted advertising by:FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=adsGOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymousBING - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-adsAdditionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.DO NOT TRACKPlease note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.YOUR RIGHTSIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.DATA RETENTIONWhen you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.CHANGESWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
CONTACT USFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at info@marymaxim.com or by telephone at 1.800.962.9504Mary Maxim Inc[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]Mary Maxim Inc, 2001 Holland Ave, Port Huron, MI 48060, United States
Copyright 2018 Mary Maxim, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
